<blog>
<post>
<title>
BRAINFERG
</title>
  
  <gallery>
"static/brainferg1.jpg"
  </gallery>

<quotebox>
white: THIS IS BRAINFERG. 
  
  ANTI-HEGELIAN POST DIALECTICAL DISCURSIVE ZONE.      
  
  ACTOR NETWORK THEORY PETER GRIFFIN FART NOISE.
</quotebox> 

  <textbox>
  is it easy to apologize? sorry, i'm not so sure; i spend a long time thinking about what comes next now, the tick or thrum, a bobble away; 
have i said that time feels slipperier (can i say that?) than before? lateral movement-slow movement-ok
  </textbox>

  <textbox>
# i think this is a manifesto, but i'm not sure for what yet
  </textbox>
  
  <textbox>
    is there a heaven for bugs? are bugs in heaven? how many bugs are in heaven?
  </textbox>

<textbox>
the weird other moment

when a car’s lights flash through the window in the garage

i, standing barefoot on the concrete, look at it

but maybe that was already obvious, implicitly so

dancing through his tiny ocean until the streetlight flickers

it’s dark at the very bottom, but i still find ways to see

a shift in the light, movement forward
  </textbox>

<textbox>
tokyo, texas, arkansas

far cross these lands, there  i saw

a million people marching

how long have we felt parched

across the seas, through the tides

and onto the sandy shore

tokyo, texas, arkansas

forever more
  </textbox>

  <textbox>
looking through his dots, i yell
hurrah vacuii! would he have really wanted to see it all?
  </textbox>

<textbox>
even if there were four different heavens for dogs, i’m not sure i’d end up in any of them; stripped away, my veins are visible—sped up, crucibled cereal, is it fine to make things up when things feel especially critical, maybe things get lost when i shift out of crisis, but i hope i can still communicate myself better than what my barks can do
  </textbox>

<quotebox>
white: WHY TF IM ALWAYS SAYING THE SAME SHIT LMAO
  </quotebox>



   <textbox>
    # JULY 15, 2021 - SPOOKY SHIT PT 1
  </textbox>
  
  <gallery>
    "static/trehant.jpg"
  </gallery>
  
  <textbox>
    1 am sunday night terrible rattling on the doorknob scared of being real scared; 
    i think i see a face in my neighbor’s tree. 
    “curled something” i tell my friends and then all i can do is laugh too;
    spinning-thin space-autumn-cicada-bush warble-living laughing loving-hahahaha-stump; 
    believing in ghosts again; ymca smell hauntology—face in the shower-granite,-real heavy—hate it, knife under the bed just in case—
    long rattling, long durée, slow pause, slow heaviness, around the corner, through the side gate, into the patio, next to the door, next to me, hopefully not next to me—terrible rattling, real scared, scared
  </textbox>
    
END OF JULY 15 2021 TRANSMISSION
  
  <textbox>
    # MAY 14, 2021 - THOUGHTS ON KORN
  </textbox>
  
  <textbox>
For some inexplicable reason, I've felt a strong draw to the band Korn recently. Constantly, [Freak on a Leash](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jRGrNDV2mKc) plays through my head, I saw the artist Lil Texas with a Korn tattoo earlier today (see below), and earlier this week, I even felt inclined to purchase a (relatively) [vintage Korn t-shirt](https://www.depop.com/products/allifisher1-rare-vintage-korn-issues-album/).
  </textbox>
    
    <gallery>
"static/brainferg2.jpg"
    </gallery>
  
    The tattoo in question 

     <textcol>
       <col>
      What can I make of all this though? I never was particularly keen on Korn when younger, and I (thanks to a fellow [bossman](https://www.tm-stnt.dev/)) only really picked up on things perhaps comparable (thinking especially of Limp Bizkit and [this track](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v290M8W-HFI), which kind of blows my mind) in the last year.
       </col>
      
   <col>
 Is this an expression of some inner angst that I've been unknowingly carrying for a long time? Perhaps! Is it a connection to my recent fascination with XXL sized t-shirts, giving me a Durstian fitment that puts me onto some strong CEO vibes? Partially, yes! 
       </col>
   </textcol>
  
  <gallery>
    "static/barrier.jpg"
  </gallery>
        
    <textcol> 
      <col>
       But more so than anything else, I think it is a reflection on the idea of new sincerity that re-entered my life, following the same earlier bossman keeping me updated with his reading of *Infinite Jest*, something which I only *barely* remember since reading it almost 5-6 years ago now, under the impression it was an unspoken required reading for being a college English Lit major. 
      </col>
        
        <col>
        There's something that I find so sincere about the act of listening to Korn itself, something that perhaps translates the feelings of transcendence I felt upon discovering [Alex G's *Race*](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1IZCY7lhs2M) last January, for example, into the quotidian. I hate to say it, as it sounds corny, but there's a reliable rawness that permeates their music that makes me just want to drink Monsters and thrash in my room. But that's all I have to say right now.
      </col>
    </textcol>
  
  <gallery>
    "static/brainferg4.jpg"
  </gallery>
    
    <textcol>
      <col>
     The track of the week is [Tony Tribe's rendition of "Red Red Wine"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PNgzk0TvJJI). 
      </col>
      
      <col>
      The garment of the week is this [Yohji Yamamoto SS14 Object Dyed T-Shirt](https://www.grailed.com/listings/21889159-yohji-yamamoto-rare-yohji-yamamoto-eat-my-fingers-object-dyed-t-shirt), which I am regrettably the new owner of. 
      </col>
     </textcol>
  
END OF MAY 14 2021 TRANSMISSION
  
  <image src="dynamic/dancingbear.gif"/>

   <textbox>
    # JULY 26 - spooky shit part 2 (more contemplative)
  </textbox>

<textcol>
<col>
  i am four thousand snakes ever present, i am always already, im 4000 snakes pulsing at the promise of the next
  </col>
<col>
the track of the week is... muddled in self-reference, here, and now, and sometimes here again; that’s fine, a tingling in the arms, a warmness in my breath, i’m circling around again
  </col>
  </textcol>
      
    </post>
    
    <preview>
      <title>
        BRAINFERG
        </title>
      

      
<image src="static/brainferg0.jpg"/>
<blurb>
MY BLOG HAHAHA
</blurb>
</preview>
   
</blog>

          
