<blog>
<post>
<title>
BRAINFERG
</title>

<quotebox>
white: THIS IS BRAINFERG. 
  
  ANTI-HEGELIAN POST DIALECTICAL DISCURSIVE ZONE.   
  
  THERE ARE MANY HIDDEN LINKS IN THESE WORDS.   
  
  ACTOR NETWORK THEORY PETER GRIFFIN FART NOISE.
</quotebox> 

<gallery>
"static/brainferg1.jpg"
  </gallery>
  
  <textbox>
    # MAY 14, 2021 - THOUGHTS ON KORN
  </textbox>
  
  <textcol>
    <col>
      For some inexplicable reason, I've felt a strong draw to the band Korn recently. Constantly, [Freak on a Leash](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jRGrNDV2mKc) plays through my head, I saw the artist Lil Texas with a Korn tattoo earlier today (see below), 
    </col>
      
    <col>
      and earlier this week, I even felt inclined to purchase a (relatively) [vintage Korn t-shirt](https://www.depop.com/products/allifisher1-rare-vintage-korn-issues-album/).
    </col>
  </textcol>
    
    <gallery>
"static/brainferg2.jpg"
    </gallery>
  
    The tattoo in question 

     <textcol>
       <col>
      What can I make of all this though? I never was particularly keen on Korn when younger, and I (thanks to a fellow [bossman](https://www.tm-stnt.dev/)) only really picked up on things perhaps comparable (thinking especially of Limp Bizkit and [this track](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v290M8W-HFI), which kind of blows my mind) in the last year.
         </col?
         
        <col> 
         Is this an expression of some inner angst that I've been unknowingly carrying for a long time? Perhaps! Is it a connection to my recent fascination with XXL sized t-shirts, giving me a Durstian fitment that puts me onto some strong CEO vibes? Partially, yes! 
       </col>
      </textcol>
        
    <textcol> 
      <col>
       But more so than anything else, I think it is a reflection on the idea of new sincerity that re-entered my life, following the same earlier bossman keeping me updated with his reading of *Infinite Jest*, something which I only *barely* remember since reading it almost 5-6 years ago now, under the impression it was an unspoken required reading for being a college English Lit major. 
      </col>
        
        <col>
        There's something that I find so sincere about the act of listening to Korn itself, something that perhaps translates the feelings of transcendence I felt upon discovering [Alex G's *Race*](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1IZCY7lhs2M) last January, for example, into the quotidian. I hate to say it, as it sounds corny, but there's a reliable rawness that permeates their music that makes me just want to drink Monsters and thrash in my room. But that's all I have to say right now.
      </col>
    </textcol>
    
    <textcol>
      <col>
     The track of the week is [Tony Tribe's rendition of "Red Red Wine"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PNgzk0TvJJI). 
      </col>
      
      <col>
      The garment of the week is this [Yohji Yamamoto SS14 Object Dyed T-Shirt](https://www.grailed.com/listings/21889159-yohji-yamamoto-rare-yohji-yamamoto-eat-my-fingers-object-dyed-t-shirt), which I am regrettably the new owner of. 
      </col>
     </textcol>
  
  End of May 14 2021 Transmission
      
    </post>
    
    <preview>
      <title>
        BRAINFERG
        </title>
      
<image src="static/brainferg0.jpg"/>
<blurb>
MY BLOG HAHAHA
</blurb>
</preview>
   
</blog>

          
   
 
   
 
                
                
     
           
          
      
